Finding Aid for the Preston Sturges Papers LSC.1114
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Production Material
  - Revolt of the Women
    - Production correspondence., 1941.; 1 piece. (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Title., 1941.; 3 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Road to Rome (Play, Produced ), 1953
    - Contracts., 1953.; 8 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence., 1952-1953.; 11 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Road to Rome (Projected Film)
    - Correspondence., 1955-1957.; 14 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - ---., 1958.; 10 pieces in each of 3 folders. (Box 41, Folder 42-44)
    - ---., 1958.; 13 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 45)
    - ---., 1959.; 10 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - ---., 1959.; 7 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - ---., n.d.; 5 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Rock-A-Bye Baby (Paramount. ), 1958
    - Correspondence., 1958.; 3 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Safeguarding Military Information (United States Army. ), 1941
    - Correspondence., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Silk Stockings
    - Screenplay and synopsis., 1932.; 19 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - The Silver Swan
    - Agreement., 1930.; 3 items. (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - The Sin of Harold Diddlebock (United Artists. ), 1947
    - Article., n.d.; 10 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Budget and operations reports., 1945-1946.; 32 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Casting. v.p., v.d.; 20 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Censorship., 1945.; 2 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence., 1945-1949.; 10 leaves in each of 7 folders. (Box 42, Folder 5-11)
    - ---., 7 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Production notes., 1944-1947.; 30 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Publicity., ca. 1947.; 5 items. (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Shooting schedule., 1946.; 12 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Slaughter House: a Murder Play in 3 Acts
    - Script. n.p., 1931.; 16 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Song of Joy
    - Correspondence., 1936-1941.; 3 pieces. (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Synopsis. n.p., n.d.; 19 leaves. Typescript. (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Spinster Dinner and Next Time We Love
    - Correspondence., 1935.; 1 leaf. (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Credits., 1935.; 2 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - The Story of Leif Ericson
    - Notes., 1957.; 2 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Strictly Dishonorable (Play, Produced ), 1929
    - Casting., 1931.; 6 pieces. (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Clippings., 16 items. (Box 42, Folder 22a)
    - Contracts., 1929-1938.; 17 pieces. (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence., 1929-1930.; 13 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - ---., 1931-1949.; 9 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - ---., 1950.; 10 leaves in each of two folders. (Box 42, Folder 26-27)
    - ---., 1952-1957.; 12 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - ---., 1958-n.d.; 4 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Notebook., 1929.; 1 item. (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Notes., n.d.; 13 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Publicity., n.d. (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Radio adaption., 1942.; 19 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - The Strong Box
    (Also known as: The Human Strung Box; The Living Strong Box; Le Coffre-Fort Vivant)
    - Correspondence., 1941-1943.; 14 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Synopses., 1938-1943.; 14 leaves. (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Sullivan's Travels (Paramount. ), 1941
    - Cast and crew., 1941.; 18 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Censorship., 1941.; 9 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - general., 1941.; 12 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ---., 1942.; 10 leaves in each of two folders. (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
    - ---., 1942.; 11 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - ---., 1942.; 15 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Crowther, Boxley., 1942.; 1 leaf. (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - ---. Wright, Frank Lloyd., 1942.; 1 leaf. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - general., 1943-1948.; 10 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Previews and reviews., 1941.; 13 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Production notes., 1941.; 10 leaves in each of two folders. (Box 43, Folder 12-13)
    - ---., 5 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Publicity., n.d.; 2 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Research notes., 1941.; 5 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Screenplay. Revised pages., 1941.; 54 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Set design., n.d.; 3 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Shooting schedule., 1941.; 10 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Tea and Sympathy
    - Correspondence - Dietrich, Marlene., 1957.; 2 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Television Appearances: Open End
    - Correspondence and notes., 1959.; 6 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Television Ideas
    - Miscellaneous - Correspondence., 1953-1958.; 14 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous - Notes., n.d.; 4 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Les aventures galantes. Notes., 1958.; 7 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - It happened exactly here. Correspondence., 1952-1959.; 5 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - It happened exactly here. Notes., n.d.; 16 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Omnibus (CBS) Correspondence., 1953.; 5 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Omnibus (CBS) Notes., 1959.; 6 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Plays I Always Wanted to See Again. Notes., 1959.; 4 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Station F.A.T.E. Correspondence., 1953-1959.; 7 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - They still live. Notes., n.d.; 1 leaf. (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Your story (TeeVee Company) Script notes. 33 leaves., 1953. (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - You be the witness. Notes., n.d.; 17 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - The Terrible Tempered Mr. Bangs
    - Story idea., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Thirty Day Princess (Paramount. ), 1934
    - Correspondence., 1934-1949.; 8 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Three Black Pennies
    - Agreement and assignment., 1944.; 5 items. (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence., 1943-1954.; 10 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - ---. l1 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - ---. 9 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - A Twenty-Four Hour Affair
    - Correspondence., 1959.; 2 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Unfaithfully Yours (Twentieth Century Fox. ), 1948
    - Assignment., 1947.; 1 item. (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Contract., 1946-1947.; 14 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence., 1933-1947.; 7 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - ---. Zanuck, Darryl., 8 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - ---., 1948.; 18 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - ---., 1949.; 13 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - Law suits., 1948-1949.; 5 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - Notes., 1947-1948.; 16 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Production notes., 1948.; 14 leaves. (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - Vendetta (RKO. ), 1950
    (Also know as: Colomba)
    - Assignment. Los Angeles., August 17, 1945.; 1 leaf. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Budget., 1946.; 25 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence., 1945-1946.; 10 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ---., 5 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Mason, James., 1946.; 9 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Production notes., 1945-1946.; 15 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - The Volga Boatmen
    - Budget and correspondence., 1958.; 5 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - The Wedding of the Painted Moll
    - Correspondence., 1949.; 3 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - The Well of Romance (Play, Produced ), 1930
    - Agreement and contracts., 1930.; 15 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Bills and invoices, unsorted., ca. 1930. (Box 44, Folder 10-13)
    - Box office statements., 1930.; 16 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Cast and crew., 1930.; 5 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - general., 1930-1959.; 15 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Jacquet, Maurice., 1929-1939.; 14 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Financial statements., 2 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Notes., 12 leaves. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Operetta., 1930.; 1 item. (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Publicity., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Song lyrics., 28 leaves. Holograph and typescript (carbon). (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - The Wizard of Whispering Falls
    - Story notes., 1945-1949.; 4 items. (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Business And Professional Material
  - Addresses. Miscellaneous lists, cards and address books, v.p., v.d.; Unarranged. ca. 200 items in two folders. (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Advertisements. Miscellaneous ephemeral materials. v.p., v.d.; Unarranged. ca. 115 items in two folders. (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
  - Articles by Preston Sturges
    - An author in spite of himself. Photocopy of check from New York Times., February 7, 1942.; 2 copies. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Les beautés de Paris. Paris., July 14, 1958.; 5 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Causerie de Preston Sturges au centre culturel Américain. Paris., February 19, 1958.; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - How to get your man. Los Angeles []., 1943; 2 leaves. Typescript. (Box 45, Folder 8)
      Scope and Contents note
      With this: correspondence. 1 item.
    - Howard Hughes is salad champion. Los Angeles., August 12, 1946.; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Inside looking out. [Paris], March 5, 1958.; 2 leaves. Typescript. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Languages Self-Taught
    - French self-taught. n.p. [and] Latin self-taught. n.p., n.d. n.d.; 1 leaf. Typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - La langue franglaise. [Paris], July 26, 1958.; 5 leaves. Typescript. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - --. Another copy (Incomplete)., 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - [Preface and quotations concerning Spanish grammar book] Los Angeles., March 6, 1944.; 2 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Regles de la farce. [Paris], n.d.; 1 leaf. Typescript. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Rules for box-office appeal. n.p., n.d.; 2 copies of 1 leaf. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Your Paris and mine. [Paris], November 28, 1958.; 2 leaves. Holograph. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - --. Another copy (Incomplete)., Holograph. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Articles Concerning Preston Sturges
    - Five film writers instead of one. In: The London Times Weekly Review. London., May 7, 1953.; 1 leaf. Clipping. (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Hollywood's enfant terrible settles in Paris. n.p., January 25, 1955.; 1 leaf. Mimeograph. (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - The McLean residence at 125 East 54th Street. In: Architecture. New York. Sturges' residence., August 1921. 1931-1932.; 4 1eaves. Clipping. (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Mama's boy, by Alexander King. n.p. Published in Vogue Magazine., June, 1944. June 1944.; 14 leaves. Typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - [Untitled article] n.p. Published in Mademoiselle., May, 1941. May 1941.; 1 leaf. Typescript. (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - [Untitled article] n.p., April 17, 1946.; 2 leaves. Typescript. (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - [Untitled article] n.p., n.d.; 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Autobiography - The Events Leading Up to My Death
    - ---. n.p., June 17, 1944.; 8 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - ---. New York., 1959.; ca. 200 clipped pieces from typed preliminary draft. Typescript with holograph corrections and holograph. (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - ---. Paris., September 5, 1958.; 3 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. In French. (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - ---. Paris., n.d.; 12 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. In French. (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - ---. Notes. n.p., n.d.; 11 leaves. Typescript, typescript (carbon) and holograph. (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - ---. Correspondence. v.p., v.d.; 10 items. (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - ---. Contract and contractual notes. New York, ca. 1959.; 4 items. (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Automobiles
    - Includes: Correspondence, bills, insurance, certificates. v.p., v.d.; ca. 150 items. Unarranged. (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
  - Banks
    - Includes: Correspondence, checks and statements. Arranged in chronological order. v.p., 1922-1938.; ca. 100 items. (Box 46, Folder 5-7)
    - Correspondence, checks and statements. Arranged in chronological order. v.p., 1939-1959.; ca. 263 items. (Box 47, Folder 1-6)
  - Bills and Invoices
    - v.p. Unarranged., v.d.; ca. 550 items. (Box 48)
  - Boats
    - Includes: Ephemera, correspondence and advertising material. v.p. Unarranged., v.d. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Includes: Correspondence and ephemera concerning the United States Coast Guard. Unarranged., ca. 1943. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Includes: Correspondence, ephemera and drawings concerning boat engines. v.p. Unarranged., v.d. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Casting Notes
    - n.p., n.d.; 43 leaves. Typescript and typescript with holograph corrections and holograph. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Charities
    - Correspondence and ephemera. v.p., v.d.; 36 items. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Coat of Arms, Sturges Family
    - Correspondence and ephemera., ca. 1900.; 4 items. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Contract Information: Motion Picture, Miscellaneous
    - n.p., v.d.; 2 items. Typescript and holograph. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Contracts, Deeds and Leases: Non-Motion Picture
    - v.p., 1930-1948.; 21 items. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Diet
    - Includes dietary information and menus. v.p., v.d.; 11 items. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Director's Salaries
    - List of motion picture directors and their salaries. n.p., 1 item. Typescript. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Dogs
    - Correspondence, ephemera, notes, articles. v.p. Unarranged., v.d. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Drawings
    - Architectural. Miscellaneous drawings by Preston Sturges. n.p. Unarranged., n.d.; ca. 100 items. (Box 49, Folder 12, 13)
    - Mechanical. Unarranged. n.p., n.d.; ca. 50 items. (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous. n.p. Unarranged., n.d.; ca. 80 items. (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements and Personal Inventories
    - v.p., 1937-1953.; 25 items. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Identify Cards and Personal Information
    - v.p. Includes birth certificate., v.d.; 20 items. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Insurance
    - Includes: Correspondence, policies and ephemera. Arranged in chronological order. v.p., 1929-1953. (Box 50, Folder 3-7)
  - Interviews
    - [Interview with Hedda Hopper] n.p., n.d.; 4 leaves. Holograph. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - [Interview with Gross] n.p., n.d.; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - [Interviewer unknown] n.p., August 6, 1940.; 2 leaves. Typescript. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Question and answer press conference with Brazilian film editors. Rio de Janeiro., November 18, 1941.; 3 items. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Investments
    - Includes: Statements and correspondence. v.p., 1929-1931.; 97 items. (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Letterheads
    - Designs and samples. v.p., v.d.; 42 items. (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Lists
    - v.p., v.d..; 37 items. (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Marriage Certificates
    - v.p., v.d.; 2 items. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Memorabilia
    - v.p., v.d.; 4 items. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Motion Picture Credits
    - n.p., n.d.; 1 leaf. Typescript with holograph corrections. Another copy. Typescript (carbon). (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Names
    - Invented names by Preston Sturges. n.p., n.d.; 4 items. Typescript and holograph. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Notes
    - Notes - dialogue (unidentified) v.p., v.d.; 25 pieces. Typescript and holograph. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Notes - miscellaneous. v.p., v.d.; 72 items. Typescript and holograph. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Notes - story ideas. v.p., v.d.; 74 items. Typescript and holograph. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Obituary Notices
    - n.p., 1959.; 7 leaves. Typescript (carbon) manuscript of newspaper articles. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Pamphlets
    - Pamphlets - miscellaneous. v.p., v.d.; ca. 55 items. (Box 51, Folder 9-10)
    - Pamphlets - miscellaneous. v.p., v.d.; ca. 50 items. (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Patents and Inventions By Preston Sturges
    Includes:
    - Correspondence and notes. v.p., v.d.; 11 items. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Airplane. Diagram and explanation. New York., 1926.; 1 leaf (2 copies) Holograph. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Automatic bailer. Los Angeles. Diagram and explanation., June 12, 1948.; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Automobile. New York. Diagram and explanation., March 5, 1927.; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Bandsaw. Los Angeles. Diagram and explanation., November 5, 1939.; 1 leaf. Typescript and holograph. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Canned laughter. v.p. Correspondence only., 1934.; 6 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Chairs. New York. Correspondence only., 1930.; 3 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Engraved plate process. New York. Diagram and explanation., March 24, 1924.; 18 leaves. Typescript and photocopy. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Exercise apparatus. v.p. Correspondence only., 1940.; 13 leaves. Typescript and typescript(carbon). (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Hearing aid. v.p. Diagram, explanation, notes and correspondence., 1937-1948.; 48 leaves. Typescript, typescript (carbon) and holograph. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Hydraulic table. n.p. Diagram and explanation., October 18, 1943.; 2 leaves. Holograph. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Hydromatic level. n.p. Diagram and explanation., November 19, 1947.; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Low compression diesel engine. n.p. Diagram and explanation and correspondence., 1934.; 16 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon) and holograph. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Lubricating springs. New York. Diagram and explanation., July 3, 1926.; 1 leaf. Holograph. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Motion picture projection and sound track devices drawings. v.p., v.d.; 73 items. (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Motion picture projection and sound track devices notes. v.p., v.d.; 42 items. (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Motion picture projection and sound track devices correspondence. v.p., 1944-1946.; 37 leaves. (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Nail brush. Los Angeles. Explanation and correspondence., 1947-1948.; 11 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Portable car generator. Los Angeles. Diagram and explanation., November 5, 1943.; 1 item. (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Powder receptacle. v.p. Diagram and explanation., 1931-1932.; 19 leaves. (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - True image finder. n.p. Diagram., April 26, 1948.; 1 leaf. (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Tub and basin. n.p. Diagram., November 27, 1929.; 1 leaf. (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Waterproof hinge. n.p. Diagram and explanation., December 26, 1947.; 1 leaf. (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Windows in fabric. New York. Diagram and explanation., July 3, 1926.; 1 leaf. (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified sketches and notes. v.p., v.d.; 42 items. (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Not Preston Sturges. v.p., v.d.; 16 items. (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - The Players Restaurant, Los Angeles
    - Advertising and publicity., 1951-1954.; 14 items. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Architecture and design., 7 items. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Barbershop., n.d.; 6 items. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Club concept., n.d.; 6 items. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence., 1940-1943.; 86 items. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Entertainment., 1942.; 17 items. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Finances., 1942-1953.; 65 items. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Insurance., 1943.; 2 items. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Menus., v.d.; 42 items. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Theater., v.d.; 10 items. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Zoning and ordinances., 1939-1951.; 57 items. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Plays and Synopses Not By Preston Sturges
    - Plays and synopses not by Preston Sturges., 14 items. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Programs
    - Programs - miscellaneous. v.p., v.d.; 10 items. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Programs - miscellaneous, v.p., v.d.; 10 items. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Programs - miscellaneous. v.p., v.d.; 11 items. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Quotations Collected By Sturges
    - Quotations collected by Sturges., 6 items. (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Song Lyrics By Sturges
    - Song lyrics by Sturges. v.p., v.d.; 54 items. (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Speeches By Sturges
    - Speeches by Sturges. v.p., v.d.; 11 items. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Stage Plans
    - Stage plans., 1 item. (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Synopses By Sturges
    - Synopses by Sturges. v.p., v.d.; 8 pieces. (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Sturges Engineering Company, Wilmington, California
    - Advertising. v.p., v.d.; 15 items. (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence. v.p., v.d.; 35 items. (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Finances. v.p., 1941-1948.; 48 items. (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Inventory. v.p., v.d.; 46 items. (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Invoices. v.p., v.d.; 31 items. (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Lease., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Notes. v.p., v.d.; 19 items. (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Titles for possible films. n.p., v.d.; 39 items. (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Verses by Preston Sturges. n.p., n.d.; 12 leaves. (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Unsorted Newsclippings
    - Unsorted newsclippings. v.p., v.d. (Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58)
  - Unsorted Photographs
    - Unsorted photographs. (Box 59)
- Correspondence
  - A - Am., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - A - Am., 12 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - A - Am., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - A - Am., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - A - Am., 12 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - A - Am., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - A - Am., 12 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Abramson, Charles., 1932-1959
    - 1930-1932., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - 1932., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - 1932., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - 1932., 16 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - 1933., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - 1933., 13 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - 1933., 12 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - 1933., 12 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - 1933., 12 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - 1934-1959., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - 1934-1959., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - 1934-1959., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - 1934-1959., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - 1934-1959., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Alajalov., 1 piece. (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Aman, Leigh and Doone., 8 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - American Broadcasting Company, Incorporated., 1 piece. (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - American National Interests Commissary (ANIC), Paris., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - American National Interests Commissary., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - American National Interests Commissary., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - American National Interests Commissary., 7 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Amp - Ap., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Amp - Ap., 14 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Amp - Ap., 8 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Anderson, Walter., 7 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Appel, Robert., 2 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Ar - Az., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Ar - Az., 10 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Ar - Az., 11 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Ar - Az., 16 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Ar - Az., 9 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Arzner, Dorothy., 5 pieces. (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Auer, Mischa., 2 items. (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Authors' League., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 1)
    See also: [Box 97, folders 9-10].
  - Authors' League., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Authors' League., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Authors' League., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Authors' League., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Authors' League., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Authors' League., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - B - Ba., 12 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - B - Ba., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - B - Ba., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - B - Ba., 10 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - B - Ba., 16 pieces. (Box 61, Folder 12)